purebarre.com 2017-12-31

# Privacy Policy

At Pure Barre, we respect your privacy. We recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you may share with us. Your use of this site is subject to this Privacy Policy. Therefore, it is important that you fully understand the conditions of our collection and use of such information. Please take a moment and read our policy before using and/or submitting information on our website. 

**Non-Identifiable Information**   
During your visit, we may collect, store, or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this website, such as information about which of our website’s pages you have visited. This data may be analyzed for trends and statistics and allows us to improve our services to you. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**   
During your visit, we may collect data that you provide to us voluntarily such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card and other personal information. We do not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties except as provided herein. The contact information we collect may be used for internal business purposes, such as order placement, marketing plans, and to provide you with information we believe may be of interest to you. We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. 

**Changes to Your Information**   
If you prefer not to receive information from us, you may opt-out by emailing your information to [info@purebarre.com](mailto:info@purebarre.com)

 **Third-Party Sites**   
Any third-party websites linked to or from this website may have different privacy policies and practices. You should review the privacy polices on these other websites in order to determine how each website may use any personal information you provide. 

**Security**   
We use industry-standard encryption techniques when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our website. We have appropriate security measures in place at our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we may have collected from you at our site. While Pure Barre makes every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that these security measures will prevent third-parties from illegally obtaining this information. 

**Questions or Comments**   
If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [info@purebarre.com](mailto:info@purebarre.com).
